[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star Wars character ordered Wipe them out. . . all of them.?", "correct_answer": "Emperor Palpatine", "incorrect_answers": ["General Grievous", "Darth Maul", "Jango Fett"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What author of fiction wrote the eight novels known as The Kent Family Chronicles?", "correct_answer": "John Jakes", "incorrect_answers": ["Langston Hughes", "Mark Twain", "Ernest Hemingway"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the term tornado family denote?", "correct_answer": "A series of tornadoes", "incorrect_answers": ["A family that had suffered damages caused by a tornado", "A class of tornadoes", "Quarrelsome family"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the tail of these animals appears thicker,  then you could expect a severe winter.", "correct_answer": "Squirrels", "incorrect_answers": ["Bears", "Skunks", "Marmots"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Socrates describe the so-called \u2018demonic sign\u2019 that he claimed to appear to him when he was about to make a mistake?", "correct_answer": "Inner voice", "incorrect_answers": ["Natural disaster", "None of these", "Divine vision"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rodrigo Santoro played King Xerxes in the 2007 film hit 300. What TV show did he appear in at the same time?", "correct_answer": "Lost", "incorrect_answers": ["Heroes", "Desperate housewives", "ER"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Because of introducing a classification scheme for distinguishing living organisms, Carolus Linnaeus is known as the father of what field of science?", "correct_answer": "Taxonomy", "incorrect_answers": ["Zoology", "Palentology", "Botany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the predominant religion in Luxembourg?", "correct_answer": "Roman Catholic", "incorrect_answers": ["Islam", "Orthodox Catholic", "Protestant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of Jim Hensons Muppets was the first one to be a regular on The Jimmy Dean Show?", "correct_answer": "Rowlf  the Dog", "incorrect_answers": ["Kermit the Frog", "Big Bird", "Oscar the Grouch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is best for cooling your mouth if you have just eaten very spicy food?", "correct_answer": "Milk", "incorrect_answers": ["Water", "White wine", "Red wine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the reproduction of cockroaches?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Male roaches use court rituals to attract the female.", "A few species can reproduce through parthenogenesis, or without the need of fertilization.", "Males and females attract each other through pheromones."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these 1997 nominees won the Razzie Award for Worst Picture?", "correct_answer": "The Postman", "incorrect_answers": ["Speed 2: Cruise Control", "Anaconda", "Batman  Robin"]}]